HOMECOMING: A film by Beyoncé is a documentary, music film directed by Beyoncé.
This intimate, in-depth look at Beyoncé's celebrated 2018 Coachella performance
reveals the emotional road from creative concept to cultural movement.
Self, played by Beyoncé.
Self - Special Guest, played by Jay-Z.
Self - Special Guest, played by Kelly Rowland.
Self - Special Guest, played by Michelle Williams.
Self - Special Guest, played by Solange.
Self, played by Blue Ivy Carter.
Homecoming: A Film by Beyoncé is a 2019 documentary concert film about American singer
Beyoncé's performance at the 2018 Coachella Valley Music and Arts Festival.
She wrote, executive-produced, and directed the film.
It was released on April 17, 2019 by Netflix,
alongside an accompanying live album.
Beyoncé's headlining performances at the 2018 Coachella
festival took place on April 14 and 21.
She was the first Black woman to headline the festival and her
performance received widespread critical acclaim.
Many in the media described the show as "historic," while The New York Times proclaimed it as "meaningful, absorbing, forceful and radical."
Her performances paid tribute to the culture of historically black
colleges and universities, featuring a full marching band and majorette dancers, while incorporating various aspects of black Greek life, such as a step show along with strolling by pledges.
The productions were also influenced by black feminism, sampling black authors and featuring on-stage appearances by fellow
Destiny's Child members Kelly Rowland and Michelle Williams, her husband Jay-Z, and her sister Solange Knowles.
The film won Best Music Film at the Grammy Awards and Best
Music Documentary at the IDA Documentary Awards.
It was also nominated for six awards at the Primetime Emmy Awards.
The film explores themes of dance performance, pop,
rhythm and blues (r&b), singer, singing.
The tone is emotional.